class QuestionAndAnswer{

  bool isExpanded;    //Is Question clicked -> Show Answer
  final String question;
  final String answer;

  QuestionAndAnswer({this.isExpanded = false, required this.question, required this.answer});
}


final List<QuestionAndAnswer> qnaList = [
  QuestionAndAnswer(question: "The actor John Gielgud believed that of all Shakespeare's characters Hamlet is probably the one most like Shakespeare himselfâ€“since, of all Shakespeare's characters, only Hamlet can be imagined to have written all the Shakespearean plays. How good an understanding of Hamlet's character does Gielgud's belief reflect?", answer: "Discuss the belief that great literature of the twentieth century lacks protagonists who qualify as heroes. (Among the works you discuss, include at least two by the following authors: Anton Chekhov, Virginia Woolf, Ernest Hemingway, F. Scott Fitzgerald, James Joyce, Gabriel Garcia Marquez, Amy Tan, Chinua Achebe.)"),
  QuestionAndAnswer(question: "header 2", answer: "body 2"),
  QuestionAndAnswer(question: "header 3", answer: "body 3"),
  QuestionAndAnswer(question: "header 4", answer: "body 4"),
  QuestionAndAnswer(question: "header 5", answer: "body 5"),
  QuestionAndAnswer(question: "header 6", answer: "body 6"),
  QuestionAndAnswer(question: "header 7", answer: "body 7"),
  QuestionAndAnswer(question: "header 8", answer: "body 8"),
  QuestionAndAnswer(question: "header 9", answer: "body 9"),
  QuestionAndAnswer(question: "header 10", answer: "body 10"),
  QuestionAndAnswer(question: "header 11", answer: "body 11"),
  QuestionAndAnswer(question: "header 12", answer: "body 12")

];